// quizData.js

export const carKnowledgeQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What should you do at a stop sign?",
    options: [
      "Stop and proceed if the way is clear",
      "Slow down and honk",
      "Ignore it and keep driving",
      'Call the police.'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who should first be prioritized on Zebra Crossing?",
    options: ["Male", "Female", "Cattle", "Pedestrian"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How would one know the speed of the vehicle ahead getting slow?",
    options: [
      "By brake Light",
      "Through the driver’s gestures",
      "If the smoke of the silencer is getting less",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Whom should be prioritized while crossing the road?",
    options: [
      "School students",
      "Physically disabled",
      "Senior Citizen",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle should be given priority while driving on road?",
    options: ["Hearse Van", "Fire brigade", "Ambulance", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done to overtake the vehicle moving ahead?",
    options: [
      "By turning on headlight",
      "By blowing horn",
      "By turning on side light",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 6,
  },
  {
    question:
      "On which side of the road do people drive their vehicle in Nepal?",
    options: [
      "Right side",
      "Left side",
      "Whatever side available",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "In which speed is the consumption of fuel low?",
    options: [
      "Slow speed",
      "Medium speed",
      "High speed",
      "Both slow and medium speed",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 8,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What would you do when you see an ambulance is following your vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Stop your vehicle",
      "Give side, let it go",
      "Increase speed",
      "Overtake it",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 9,
  },
  {
    question: "In what kind of road is most dangerous if the brake fails?",
    options: [
      "Road going uphill",
      "Road going downhill",
      "Flat road",
      "Gravel road",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "In which speed is the consumption of fuel high?",
    options: ["Slow Speed", "Medium Speed", "High speed", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 11,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle either going up or down, should give side?",
    options: [
      "Moving upward",
      "Moving downward",
      "Both of them",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which vehicle either going straight or turning round should be prioritized?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle turning round",
      "Vehicle going straight",
      "Both of them",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question: "Why should one keep on changing gear?",
    options: [
      "To decrease speed",
      "To increase speed",
      "To blow horn",
      "Both to increase or to decrease speed",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which side should be used for driving low-speed vehicle slowly in Nepal?",
    options: [
      "From middle",
      "From right",
      "From left",
      "Whatever side one prefers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 15,
  },
  {
    question: "Which part in a four-wheeler do the feet control?",
    options: ["Clutch", "Brake", "Accelerator", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 16,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which vehicle either moving upwards or moving downwards should be prioritized?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle moving downward",
      "Vehicle moving upward",
      "Side shouldn’t be given",
      "Whosoever can, should go ahead",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 17,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle doesn't move on the road?",
    options: ["Ship", "Plane", "Helicopter", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 18,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should a driver do to know whether the speed of the vehicle ahead is low or high?",
    options: [
      "By asking the driver",
      "From the gestures of the driver",
      "Guessing",
      "None of these",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 19,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the oil pressure indicator show in the vehicle?",
    options: ["Diesel", "Mobil", "Water", "Petrol"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 20,
  },
  {
    question: "When should the seat belt be used?",
    options: [
      "Those who sit at the front",
      "As soon as the police see",
      "While moving down",
      "While moving up",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 21,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle should not be prioritized first while driving?",
    options: ["Car", "Motorcycle", "Truck", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 22,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be done to allow the vehicle coming from the rear side to move ahead?",
    options: [
      "By gesturing from hand",
      "By turning on side light",
      "Both A & B",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 23,
  },
  {
    question: "In Nepal driving on which side is punishable?",
    options: ["Right side", "Left side", "Both", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 24,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main function of the left hand in four-wheelers?",
    options: [
      "To Brake",
      "To control handle",
      "To use hand brake",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 25,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should you do when you see a fire brigade coming behind you?",
    options: ["Stop the vehicle", "Give side", "Increase Speed", "Ignore"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 26,
  },
  {
    question: "What should one do while turning the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Turn the side light",
      "Lower the speed",
      "Look both sides",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 27,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle should be prioritized?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle moving downward",
      "Vehicle moving upward",
      "Both of them",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 28,
  },
  {
    question: "What should one do either to lower or increase the speed?",
    options: [
      "Change gear",
      "Press or release accelerator",
      "Both of them",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 29,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which lane of the road should be used while driving the vehicle at higher speed?",
    options: ["Middle Lane", "Side Lane", "Both of them", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 30,
  },
  {
    question: "In general, when should one turn on the headlight?",
    options: [
      "Day Time",
      "Dark/Night Time",
      "On seeing traffic police",
      "On having an accident",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 31,
  },
  {
    question: "What do we understand by a temporary route permit?",
    options: [
      "To drive on the permitted road only",
      "To get permission to drive on the road which is not stated on the regular permit",
      "To get permission to drive along the local road",
      "To drive time and again",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 32,
  },
  {
    question: "What shouldn't be done before you get a driving license?",
    options: [
      "Not to drive the vehicle",
      "Not to sit in the vehicle",
      "Not to buy the vehicle",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 33,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should one do to his or her vehicle while the VIP vehicle is on the road?",
    options: [
      "To stop and give way",
      "To blow horn",
      "To drive the vehicle",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 34,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How should one behave to the traffic police when she or he stops the vehicle showing your fault?",
    options: [
      "To insist that you haven't done anything wrong",
      "To run away from the traffic police.",
      "To realize your mistake politely.",
      "To make other drivers your witness insisting that you haven't done anything wrong",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 35,
  },
  {
    question: "How much fuel should be better to put in the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Only a little",
      "Half Tank",
      "Fill the tank if fuel is finished.",
      "Full tank if possible",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 36,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What kind of vehicle isn't allowed for use in public transportation?",
    options: [
      "Private vehicle",
      "Public vehicle",
      "Tourist vehicle",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 37,
  },
  {
    question: "What do you mean by conductor/steward/attendant?",
    options: [
      "One who drives",
      "One who has got a license to drive",
      "One who assists in the vehicle",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 38,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle has an L sign?",
    options: [
      "Government vehicle",
      "Learner's vehicle",
      "Diplomatic vehicle",
      "Public vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 39,
  },
  {
    question: "How would one signal while overtaking the vehicle ahead?",
    options: [
      "Requesting him/her to stop by phone",
      "Gesturing with hand",
      "Blowing Horn",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 40,
  },
  {
    question: "For what purpose should the looking glass be used?",
    options: ["To overtake", "To back", "Both of them", "Not of them"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 41,
  },
  {
    question: "What quality should a driver have?",
    options: ["Patience", "Sweet speaking", "Friendly", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 42,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done for a safe journey?",
    options: [
      "Follow the traffic rules",
      "Drive randomly",
      "Drive speedily",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 43,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be done while driving if anything is not visible during rain?",
    options: ["Switch wiper", "Speed up", "Stop the vehicle", "Blow horn"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 44,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Among the following options, which one isn’t in an electric vehicle?",
    options: ["Silencer pipe", "Accelerator", "Clutch", "Gear"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 45,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle is it when it has Ba 1 ba number plate?",
    options: [
      "Private motorcycle",
      "Government motorcycle",
      "Corporation's motorcycle",
      "Rental motorcycle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 46,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Among the offices mentioned below, in which office should one pay vehicular tax?",
    options: [
      "Internal Revenue Office",
      "Custom Office",
      "Transport Management Office",
      "Excise Duty Office",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 47,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done if the embossed number plate doesn't work?",
    options: [
      "To change it as one likes",
      "To change after submitting an application at the Transport Management Office",
      "To change after repairing",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 48,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle is it if it has ma 1 ng?",
    options: ["Private car", "Taxi", "Tempoo", "Corporation's jeep"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 49,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is it called if the vehicle is registered in two or more than two persons' names?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle registration",
      "Joint vehicle registration",
      "Vehicle buying or selling",
      "Vehicle ownership",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 50,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the color of Bluebook?",
    options: ["Black", "Red", "Blue", "Yellow"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 51,
  },
  {
    question: "Which are the emergency vehicles?",
    options: ["Fire brigade", "Ambulance", "Hearse van", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 52,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle is used to douse the fire?",
    options: ["Fire brigade", "Ambulance", "Hearse van", "Taxi"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 53,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Inability to differentiate which of the following color disqualifies a person from getting a driving license?",
    options: ["Red", "White", "Black", "Blue"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 54,
  },
  {
    question: "What is an embossed number plate?",
    options: [
      "Number plate written with Enamel",
      "Number plate written with etched/ brocaded /carved letter",
      "Number plate written with raised letters",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 55,
  },
  {
    question: "What is First Aid?",
    options: [
      "Taking the patient to the hospital immediately.",
      "Bandaging in ordinary injuries",
      "Calling the doctor if he/she isn't present",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 56,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle is registered in the largest number in Nepal?",
    options: ["Car", "Bus", "Motorcycle", "E-rickshaw"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 57,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the given vehicles, which one should not be registered?",
    options: [
      "Electric cycle",
      "Electric cycle with pedal",
      "Electric scooter",
      "Electric motorcycle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 58,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What happens if one changes the color of the vehicle with his/her own desire?",
    options: ["Looks good", "Looks clean", "Grows Expenses", "Deserves a fine"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 59,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which vehicle is used to carry patients/sick people to the hospital?",
    options: ["Fire brigade", "Ambulance", "Hearse van", "Taxi"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 60,
  },
  {
    question: "What does a vehicle with a green number plate indicate?",
    options: [
      "Private Vehicle",
      "Government vehicle",
      "Corporate vehicle",
      "Tourist vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 61,
  },
  {
    question: "Why is a driving license necessary?",
    options: [
      "To drive a vehicle",
      "To buy a vehicle",
      "To sell a vehicle",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 62,
  },
  {
    question: "What is a vehicle registration certificate/blue book?",
    options: [
      "Certificate with complete description of the vehicle.",
      "License to drive a vehicle",
      "Certificate with permission to drive a vehicle",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 63,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle has a black number plate?",
    options: [
      "Government vehicle",
      "Public vehicle",
      "Corporation vehicle",
      "Tourist vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 64,
  },
  {
    question:
      "With what documents should one submit an application to the office if the driving license is lost?",
    options: [
      "Application and fee with traffic police recommendation letter",
      "Recommendation from municipal ward office",
      "Recommendation letter from District Administration Office",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 65,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Among the following options, which condition is considered as disqualification to get the driving license?",
    options: [
      "Visual impairment",
      "Night blindness",
      "Having weak legs & hands",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 66,
  },
  {
    question: "Which office doesn't work for the renewal of the license?",
    options: [
      "Traffic Police Office",
      "Vehicle Fitness Test Center",
      "Department of Transport Management",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 67,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which office issues the license certificate before permitting the public vehicle to move on the road?",
    options: [
      "District Administration Office",
      "Traffic Police Office",
      "Transport Management Office",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 68,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle isn't allowed to operate without a route permit?",
    options: [
      "Private vehicle",
      "Government Vehicle",
      "Public vehicle",
      "Diplomatic vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 69,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which office has the right to change the permissible speed limit confirmed for the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Traffic Police Office",
      "Transport Management Office",
      "Department of Transport Management",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 70,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done before driving out of order vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Repair.",
      "Fill up engine.",
      "Nothing to be done.",
      "Show the police.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 71,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the chairperson of the Transportation Management Committee?",
    options: [
      "Chief of Transport Management Office",
      "District Police Chief",
      "Chief of Traffic Police Office",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 72,
  },
  {
    question: "How should one drive the vehicle along the three-lane road?",
    options: [
      "From both sides",
      "From three sides",
      "From one side",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 73,
  },
  {
    question: "How would you start your four-wheelers?",
    options: [
      "By checking gear",
      "By jamming on brake",
      "By checking oil",
      "By checking engine",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 74,
  },
  {
    question: "Why should one change gear?",
    options: ["Increase speed", "Decrease speed", "Blow horn", "Both a & b"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 75,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what condition can one not get the copy of a driving license?",
    options: [
      "Having lost the license",
      "Having torn",
      "Having old & torn",
      "Having the original with him/herself",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 76,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which signal should one give while moving ahead after starting the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "By turning on the headlight",
      "By turning on the right side light",
      "By turning on the left side light",
      "By turning on the emergency light",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 77,
  },
  {
    question: "In which place should one lower the speed of the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "School area",
      "Crossroads",
      "Densely populated area",
      "All of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 78,
  },
  {
    question: "Which one isn’t among the heavy equipment?",
    options: ["Dozer", "Mini bus", "Loader", "Mobile crane"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 79,
  },
  {
    question: "When was the first vehicle brought to Nepal?",
    options: ["B.S. 1996", "B.S. 2021", "B.S. 2000", "B.S. 2049"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 80,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the color of the fog light?",
    options: ["Red", "Yellow", "Green", "Blue"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 81,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Why is the spelling of ambulance written in a mirror image format?",
    options: [
      "So that it could be read rightly from the looking glass of the vehicle ahead",
      "As it is the convention",
      "To show the difference from others",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 82,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the blue number plate in a vehicle indicate?",
    options: [
      "Diplomatic vehicle",
      "Government vehicle",
      "Private vehicle",
      "Vehicle of Corporation",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 83,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which certificate is first needed by a Nepali citizen to obtain a driving license?",
    options: [
      "Certificate given by a driving school",
      "Health Certificate",
      "Nepali citizen certificate",
      "Educational qualification certificate",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 84,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the process followed to re-register a vehicle in another Transport Management Office?",
    options: [
      "Transfer registration",
      "Renewal",
      "Re-registration",
      "Inter-zonal registration",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 85,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whose duty is it to operate the exam of the driving license dignified?",
    options: [
      "Transport Management Office",
      "Examinees",
      "Traffic Police`s",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 86,
  },
  {
    question: "What time is known as peak hour?",
    options: [
      "Morning time",
      "Evening time",
      "One hour before and after the office opens and closes",
      "Breakfast/Lunch hour",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 87,
  },
  {
    question: "For which vehicle, third party insurance is mandatory?",
    options: [
      "Rental bus, truck",
      "Motorcycle",
      "Private Car",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 88,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the chairperson of the driving license examination committee?",
    options: [
      "Chief of Transport Management Office",
      "Chief of the Department of Transport Management",
      "Chief of Traffic Police Office",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 89,
  },
  {
    question: "What do you mean by third party insurance?",
    options: [
      "Passenger’s insurance",
      "Pedestrian’s insurance",
      "Vehicle's Insurance",
      "Driver's insurance",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 90,
  },
  {
    question: "Which office’s vehicle has a yellow number plate?",
    options: [
      "Government vehicle",
      "Private vehicle",
      "Public vehicle",
      "Corporation vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 91,
  },
  {
    question: "From which side should one alight after the vehicle stops?",
    options: ["Left side", "Right side", "Back side", "Front side"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 92,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what condition can one obtain the duplicate copy of a driving license?",
    options: [
      "Having lost",
      "Having torn",
      "Having stolen",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 93,
  },
  {
    question: "What would you do when you find someone’s driving license?",
    options: [
      "Tearing and throwing",
      "Bring it home",
      "Submit it to the traffic police",
      "Ignore it",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 94,
  },
  {
    question: "Which vehicle doesn't need a route permit?",
    options: ["Motorcycle", "Public truck", "Public jeep", "Public bus"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 95,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which office is primarily responsible for managing the movement of vehicles?",
    options: [
      "District Administration Office",
      "Transport Management Office",
      "District Police Office",
      "Traffic Police Office",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 96,
  },
  {
    question: "What educational qualification is needed for a driving license?",
    options: [
      "SLC/SEE",
      "Plus 2 or equivalent",
      "Higher Education",
      "Literate",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 97,
  },
  {
    question: "When was the Department of Transport established?",
    options: ["V.S. 2051", "V.S. 2041", "V.S. 2052", "V.S. 2042"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 98,
  },
  {
    question: "What is given more consideration while driving during rain?",
    options: ["Brake", "Skidding", "Caution to spread mud", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 99,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle’s ownership shouldn’t be transferred?",
    options: [
      "Those which crossed 20 years by production year.",
      "Those which crossed 15 years by production year.",
      "Those which crossed 5 years by production year.",
      "Those which crossed 25 years by production year.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 100,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be done if the auctioned vehicle is to be auctioned once again?",
    options: [
      "Auctioned again.",
      "Use it without registration.",
      "Scrapped as per the law.",
      "Register for auction as per the rule.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 101,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many hours should a long route public vehicle take a break?",
    options: [
      "Every three hours",
      "Every four hours",
      "Every two hours",
      "Every one hour",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 102,
  },
  {
    question: "Which office renews the driving license?",
    options: [
      "Transportation Management office.",
      "Department of Transport Management",
      "Vehicle Fitness Test Center",
      "Traffic Police Office.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 103,
  },
  {
    question: "On what kind of road should we not drive the public vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Not pitched.",
      "Gravel road.",
      "Route not allowed.",
      "Hilly road.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 104,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What kind of vehicle wouldn’t have the provision of vehicular tax?",
    options: [
      "Government vehicle.",
      "Corporation vehicle",
      "Diplomatic vehicle.",
      "Applies to all",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 105,
  },
  {
    question: "What would you do if the engine block of the vehicle breaks?",
    options: [
      "To get it changed at the workshop.",
      "To get it changed after you get permission from Transportation Management Office.",
      "To insert old vehicle’s engine block",
      "To get it changed at the market immediately when it breaks.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 106,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is it called to transform a foreign driving license into Nepal?",
    options: [
      "Internationalization.",
      "Foreignization.",
      "Transforming into Nepali (Nepalization).",
      "Nationalization",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 107,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What kind of test/trial examination should be taken to transform a foreign driving license into Nepali?",
    options: ["Written.", "Oral.", "Practical.", "None of them."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 108,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What provision is in Nepal about international/ foreign driving licenses?",
    options: [
      "Remain invalid instantly.",
      "Permission to drive across Nepal.",
      "Permission to drive only in Kathmandu valley.",
      "None of them.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 109,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of driving license’s record/data is deleted?",
    options: [
      "If not renewed till five years after renewal time is finished.",
      "Having an old license.",
      "The driving license of those who had done an accident.",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 110,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When should one go to the office for biometrics after filling the application form for a driving license?",
    options: [
      "Next day.",
      "Within one year.",
      "Within three months.",
      "Visit date given by the system.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 111,
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of road is up to 25 KM long?",
    options: ["Long road.", "Short road.", "Local road.", "Medium-sized road."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 112,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Among the given vehicles, which one shouldn’t take the route permit?",
    options: ["Ambulance.", "Fire brigade.", "Motorcycle.", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 113,
  },
  {
    question:
      "For what kind of vehicle can the authorized officer renew for up to five years?",
    options: [
      "Government.",
      "Corporation & diplomatic",
      "Private",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 114,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle is a fire brigade?",
    options: [
      "Passenger carrier.",
      "Goods carriers.",
      "Hearse Van.",
      "Fire controller.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 115,
  },
  {
    question: "What happens if one keeps pressing on the accelerator?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle doesn't work.",
      "Traffic police charges a fine.",
      "Vehicle speeds up.",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 116,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which entity do the transportation management offices come under?",
    options: [
      "Department of Transport Management",
      "Provincial Ministry for Physical Infrastructure Development",
      "Ministry for Physical Infrastructure & Transportation",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 117,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what condition do the vehicles maintain a wide distance between each other while driving?",
    options: [
      "During the time of the visit of distinguished personalities.",
      "During sunshine.",
      "When it's not raining.",
      "During foggy/misty time",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 118,
  },
  {
    question: "What shouldn’t be done while driving?",
    options: [
      "To talk on mobile.",
      "To use an alcoholic drink.",
      "To overtake randomly.",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 119,
  },
  {
    question: "How should we cross the road?",
    options: [
      "Stopping while walking.",
      "Running.",
      "Slowly through the zebra crossing.",
      "Walking smoothly",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 120,
  },
  {
    question: "What happens to those who blow the pressure horns?",
    options: [
      "Imprisonment",
      "Fine.",
      "Confiscation of the vehicle.",
      "Nothing happens",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 121,
  },
  {
    question: "What do the marks in the middle of the road indicate?",
    options: [
      "Not to race.",
      "To divide the road lane.",
      "Not to cross the road.",
      "Not to overtake.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 122,
  },
  {
    question: "Where should the bluebook be kept?",
    options: ["At home.", "With drivers", "At the office.", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 123,
  },
  {
    question: "When are the side lights turned on?",
    options: [
      "While changing lane.",
      "While overtaking.",
      "While parking the vehicle.",
      "Both a & b",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 124,
  },
];

export const carVehicularKnowledge = [
  {
    question:
      "Within how much time does one have to inform once the driving licence is lost ?",
    options: ["Seven days.", "Fifteen days.", "One month.", "Two months."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Upto how much time does one not have to pay the fine to renew the driving license once the validity period is finished?",
    options: ["One month", "Three months", "Five months", "Seven months"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How old should one be to be eligible to get car/jeep driving license ?",
    options: [
      "Sixteen years.",
      "Seventeen years.",
      "Eighteen years.",
      "Twenty years.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum no. of violations of traffic rules beyond which driving license shall be suspended?",
    options: ["Three times.", "Four times.", "Five times.", "Six times."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many years can one obtain the driving license for large vehicle once he/she has obtained the driving license for car/jeep ?",
    options: ["One year.", "Two years.", "Three years.", "Four years."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "Which office does the work of changing ownership of vehicle ?",
    options: [
      "Traffic Police Office.",
      "District Police Office.",
      "Transport Management Office.",
      "None of them.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 6,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the fee of renewing the driving license of medium vehicle ?",
    options: ["1500.", "2000.", "2500.", "3000."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "In how many years does one have to renew the driving license ?",
    options: ["5-5 years.", "3-3 Years.", "2-2 Years.", "7-7 Years."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 8,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much does one have to pay as fee to obtain jeep driving license ?",
    options: ["1 thousand.", "7 hundred.", "2 thousand.", "15 hundred."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 9,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how much time does one have to inform the office if the driver changes his/her address ?",
    options: ["7 days", "15 days.", "1 month.", "45 days."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 10,
  },

  {
    question: "How many seats are reserved for female in public vehicle ?",
    options: ["Two seats", "Three seats.", "Six seats.", "Five seats."],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 11,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how much time does one not have to pay fine to renew the bluebook once its date is expired ?",
    options: ["1 month.", "2 months.", "3 months.", "4 months."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 12,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many hours does the driver of long-distance public vehicle have to change his shift?",
    options: ["4 hours.", "6 hours.", "8 hours.", "As per the needs."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 13,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What punishment has been provisioned in law for the driver if he/she drives the vehicle with the intention to kill a person and the person dies?",
    options: [
      "No punishment",
      "Life imprisonment with forfeiture",
      "Life imprisonment.",
      "20 years imprisonment.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 14,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how much time does the bluebook become invalid if it isn't timely renewed ?",
    options: ["1 year.", "3 years,", "5 years.", "7 years."],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 15,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much fee does one have to pay if he/she adds a large vehicle in the category of his/her driving license?",
    options: [
      "5 hundred.",
      "1 thousand.",
      "1 thousand 5 hundred.",
      "2 thousand",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 16,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much fee does one have to pay to fill up the application for a driving license ?",
    options: ["Rs. 100", "Rs. 500", "Rs 300", "Rs. 400"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 17,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many years old public vehicles aren't allowed to be operated?",
    options: ["10 Years", "15 years.", "20 years.", "25 years."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 18,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much does one have to pay to renew the license for a motorcycle ?",
    options: ["1500.", "2000.", "2500", "3000"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 19,
  },
  {
    question: "What amount has been provisioned for third-party insurance ?",
    options: ["2 Lakh.", "3 Lakh.", "4 Lakh.", "5 Lakh."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 20,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many hours do the long-distance public vehicles have to take a break on the road ?",
    options: [
      "Every three hours.",
      "Every four hours.",
      "Every two hours.",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 21,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the validity period of a driving license ?",
    options: ["One year.", "Three years.", "Five years.", "Ten years."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 22,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many seats are reserved for physically disabled people in a large public vehicle that runs along the local road ?",
    options: ["Two seats.", "Three seats.", "Four seats.", "Five seats."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 23,
  },
  {
    question: "How long can a driving license be suspended?",
    options: ["Three months.", "Five months.", "Six months.", "Eight months."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 24,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much does one have to pay to renew the driving license for large vehicles ?",
    options: ["1500", "2000.", "2500.", "Not of them"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 25,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how much time from the expiry date does one have to pay a fine to renew the driving license?",
    options: ["One month.", "Three months.", "Five months.", "Seven months."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 26,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much rupee ticket has to be pasted on the application form for the route permit & change of ownership ?",
    options: ["Five rupees.", "Ten rupees.", "Two rupees.", "One rupee."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 27,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how much time does one have to submit the application for the copy of a driving license if it is lost or spoiled?",
    options: ["3 days.", "7 days.", "15 days.", "30 days."],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 28,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What provision of punishment has been made if the vehicle without a pollution pass sticker enters the prohibited area?",
    options: [
      "Imprisonment",
      "Confiscation of vehicle",
      "Restriction to drive in future.",
      "Fine for the driver.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 29,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much additional fine does one have to pay for the renewal of a driving license after one year of the due renewal date?",
    options: ["150 percent.", "50 percent.", "30 percent.", "100 percent."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 30,
  },
  {
    question:
      "As per the Vehicle and Transport Management Act, what age one must have reached for obtaining the license for a large vehicle?",
    options: ["16 years.", "18 years.", "21 years.", "25 years."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 31,
  },
  {
    question: "How often is the pollution of a private vehicle tested?",
    options: [
      "Every 3 months",
      "Every six months.",
      "Every 1 year.",
      "Every 2 years",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 32,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how much time does one have to register his/her vehicle after he/she clarifies the custom dues ?",
    options: ["Ten days.", "Fifteen days.", "Twenty days.", "Twenty-five days"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 33,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the limitation of the weight of a large vehicle ?",
    options: [
      "More than 10 ton.",
      "From 4 ton to 10 ton.",
      "Less than 4 ton.",
      "1 ton.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 34,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the limitation of the weight of a medium-sized vehicle",
    options: [
      "10 ton.",
      "From 1 ton to 4 ton.",
      "For 4 ton to 10 ton.",
      "1 ton.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 35,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the limitation of the weight of a small-sized vehicle ?",
    options: ["10 ton", "Less than 4 ton.", "Less than 1 ton.", "1 ton."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 36,
  },
  {
    question: "When was the Vehicle & Transport Management Act enacted?",
    options: ["V.S 2048.", "V.S. 2049.", "V.S. 2054.", "V.S. 2050"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 37,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the vehicular pollution standard prevailing in Nepal?",
    options: [
      "Nepal Vehicle Mass Emission Standard, 2056",
      "Nepal Vehicle Mass Emission Standard, 2060",
      "Nepal Vehicle Mass Emission Standard, 2065",
      "Nepal Vehicle Mass Emission Standard, 2069",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 38,
  },
  {
    question: "How often does one have to renew the bluebook?",
    options: [
      "Every 6 months.",
      "Every 1 year.",
      "Every 2 years.",
      "Every 4 years.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 39,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Upto how many years can one renew his/her driving license by paying a fine once it is expired?",
    options: ["5 Years", "3 years.", "2 years", "7 years"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 40,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how much time does one have to pay the license fee after he/she has passed the trial for a driving license?",
    options: ["18 months", "5 years", "15 days", "90 days"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 41,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is/are the condition(s) in which a driving license can be invalid?",
    options: [
      "If proved disqualified as per the act.",
      "If the driver dies.",
      "If the person wants to cancel it voluntarily",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 42,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Upto how much time is one who has misconducted in the written exam of a driving license not allowed to enroll in such an exam?",
    options: ["1 year.", "2 months.", "3 months.", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 43,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum time upto which a temporary vehicle registration certificate remains valid?",
    options: ["1 month.", "3 months.", "6 months", "1 year"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 44,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the road that covers more than a 250-kilometer distance called?",
    options: ["Long road.", "Local road.", "Short road.", "None of them."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 45,
  },
  {
    question:
      "For driving which vehicle is a 21 years (or more) old person eligible?",
    options: ["Small.", "Medium.", "Large.", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 46,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much fine has been provisioned if one drives without getting a driving license?",
    options: [
      "Rs. 200 to 500.",
      "Only rs. 400",
      "Rs. 500 to 2000.",
      "Upto rs.100.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 47,
  },
  {
    question: "How long does the probation period of a driving license?",
    options: ["6 months.", "1 year.", "3 months.", "18 months."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 48,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much time is added to the validity period in a driving license if a category is added.",
    options: ["5 years.", "3 months", "not increase", "18 months."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 49,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Upto how long time in maximum has the temporary route permit been provisioned?",
    options: ["14 days.", "7 days.", "5 days.", "One month."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 50,
  },
  {
    question: "How long does the route permit remain valid once it is taken?",
    options: ["4 months.", "6 months.", "3 months.", "1 year."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 51,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how many days does one have to renew the route permit once it is expired?",
    options: ["4 days.", "6 days.", "15 days.", "1 year."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 52,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What percent extra fee does one have to pay to renew the route permit for one month after it is expired?",
    options: [
      "50 percent.",
      "25 percent.",
      "100 percent.",
      "No additional charge",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 53,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how many days does one have to take a route permit after its fitness test?",
    options: ["45 days.", "60 days.", "90 days.", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 54,
  },
  {
    question:
      "As per the new procedure, what minimum percent marks does one have to obtain to pass the written exam for a driving license?",
    options: ["50 percent.", "60 percent.", "80 percent.", "70 percent."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 55,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What punishment is provisioned for those who hijack a moving vehicle and change its course?",
    options: [
      "Imprisonment or fine.",
      "Confiscation of the vehicle.",
      "Banishing from the nation.",
      "All of them.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 56,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how many days does one have to return his/her canceled driving license to the competent authority?",
    options: ["7 days.", "14 days.", "35 days.", "15 days"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 57,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What punishment is provisioned if one drives a vehicle changing a number plate?",
    options: [
      "6 months imprisonment.",
      "5 to 15 thousand fine.",
      "Confiscation of the vehicle.",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 58,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much insurance amount has been provisioned for a public vehicle driver and other employees?",
    options: ["Rs. 500,000.", "Rs. 200,000.", "Rs. 3,00,000.", "Rs. 600,000"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 59,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the maximum length of a local road?",
    options: [
      "Upto 150 kilometers.",
      "Up to 50 kilometers",
      "Upto 25 kilometers",
      "Longer than 250 kilometers",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 60,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the percentage concession of fare provisioned for senior citizens in a public vehicle?",
    options: ["5 percent.", "50 percent.", "15 percent.", "20 percent."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 61,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many years of production shall a vehicle not be registered as a public or other types of vehicle?",
    options: ["20 years.", "15 years.", "5 years.", "25 years."],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 62,
  },
  {
    question:
      "After how many years of expiry of registration can a vehicle be re-registered?",
    options: ["3 years.", "15 years.", "7 years.", "5 years."],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 63,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is considered a long-distance road?",
    options: [
      "Less than 100 KM road.",
      "Longer than 250 KM road",
      "Less than 25 KM road.",
      "None of them.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 64,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is considered a medium-distance road?",
    options: [
      "Longer than 250 KM road",
      "Road between 100 to 250 KM.",
      "Less than 25 KM road.",
      "Road between 25 to 100 KM.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 65,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is considered a short-distance road?",
    options: [
      "Longer than 250 KM road",
      "Road between 100 to 250 KM.",
      "Less than 25 KM road.",
      "Road between 25 to 100 KM.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 66,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum period for which a foreign one-time or cumulative validity period of a temporary registration certificate?",
    options: ["4 months.", "6 months.", "14 months.", "5 years."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 67,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the maximum period for a foreign-registered vehicle which can be permitted to operate in Nepal?",
    options: ["1 month.", "1 year", "5 years", "Not allowed"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 68,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much does one have to pay to change the ownership of a vehicle?",
    options: [
      "50% amount of vehicle registration charge.",
      "Rs. 5000.",
      "Whatever is needed for registration charge.",
      "Rs. 1500.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "50% amount of vehicle registration charge.",
    id: 69,
  },
  {
    question:
      "If registration certificate is suspended, within how many days does one have to submit Vehicle Registration Certificate with the written order of authorized officer?",
    options: ["7 days.", "15 days.", "35 days.", "21 days."],
    correctAnswer: "7 days.",
    id: 70,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following exams is not required for an applicant to add category in the driving license?",
    options: ["Written.", "Practical.", "Both of them.", "None of them."],
    correctAnswer: "None of them.",
    id: 71,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the minimum marks required to pass the practical exams of driving license of Category B?",
    options: ["50 percent.", "60 percent.", "70 percent.", "80 percent."],
    correctAnswer: "50 percent.",
    id: 72,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What will happen if an examinee touches the boundary line making U-turn in the practical exam for driving license of Category B (car / jeep / delivery van)?",
    options: [
      "10 marks decreases.",
      "15 marks decreases.",
      "Declares failure.",
      "Nothing happens.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Declares failure.",
    id: 73,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the marks that one can secure upon successful completion of 8 (eight) formation for driving license of Category B?",
    options: ["10 marks.", "20 marks.", "15 marks.", "25 marks."],
    correctAnswer: "20 marks.",
    id: 74,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the permissible number of engine stoppage in trial exam of Category B?",
    options: ["1 time.", "2 times.", "3 times.", "4 times."],
    correctAnswer: "1 time.",
    id: 75,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much marks is deducted if the examinee starts driving without using seatbelt in the trial exam for the driving license of Category B (car / jeep / delivery van)?",
    options: [
      "2 marks.",
      "4 marks.",
      "No mark decreases.",
      "Declared unqualified.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Declared unqualified.",
    id: 76,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the width of garage track in the garage parking section exam of trial exam of driving license of Category B (Car / Jeep / Delivery Van)?",
    options: ["2 meters.", "3 meters.", "4 meters.", "5 meters."],
    correctAnswer: "3 meters.",
    id: 77,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much marks is deducted if the examinee doesn't follow traffic signal in the trial exam for driving license of Category B (car / jeep / delivery van) driver's license?",
    options: ["10 marks.", "15 marks.", "20 marks.", "No mark decreases."],
    correctAnswer: "No mark decreases.",
    id: 78,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the length of test track used for speed breaker (ramp test) in the practical exam for driving license of Category B (car / jeep / delivery van)?",
    options: ["12 meters.", "14 meters.", "16 meters.", "20 meters."],
    correctAnswer: "12 meters.",
    id: 79,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within what duration of passing the written exam, can one appear in the trial exam?",
    options: [
      "Up to 6 months.",
      "Up to 9 months.",
      "Up to 12 months.",
      "Up to 18 months.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Up to 6 months.",
    id: 80,
  },

  {
    question:
      "For how many times can one appear in the trial exam once he/she passes the written exam?",
    options: ["1 time.", "2 times.", "3 times.", "4 times."],
    correctAnswer: "3 times.",
    id: 81,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is understood by a public place, as per the Vehicle and Transport Management Act?",
    options: ["Bridge.", "Road.", "Footpath.", "All of the above."],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above.",
    id: 82,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the time duration by which a private vehicle owner has to pay vehicular tax?",
    options: [
      "End of Ashar.",
      "End of Chitra.",
      "End of Ashwin.",
      "Within 3 months after the date ends.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Within 3 months after the date ends.",
    id: 83,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Within how many days does one have to return the canceled driving license?",
    options: [
      "Within ten days.",
      "Within fifteen days.",
      "Within thirty days.",
      "None of them.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Within thirty days.",
    id: 84,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following categories is the tourist vehicle equivalent to?",
    options: [
      "Public vehicle.",
      "Private vehicle.",
      "Government vehicle.",
      "Diplomatic vehicles.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Public vehicle.",
    id: 85,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the specified seating capacity of a mini bus?",
    options: [
      "15 to 25 including driver.",
      "12 to 20 including driver.",
      "10 to 22 including driver.",
      "24 including driver.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "15 to 25 including driver.",
    id: 86,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the age limit after which one cannot acquire a driving license for large and medium-sized public vehicles?",
    options: ["55 years.", "50 years.", "60 years.", "45 years."],
    correctAnswer: "60 years.",
    id: 87,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the fee applicable for the fitness test certificate of medium and small vehicles at VFTC (Vehicle Fitness Test Center)?",
    options: ["Rs. 200.", "Rs. 400.", "Rs. 450.", "Rs. 300."],
    correctAnswer: "Rs. 200.",
    id: 88,
  },
  {
    question: "According to the Vehicle Act, what do you mean by a driver?",
    options: [
      "One who drives a vehicle.",
      "One who has got the driving license.",
      "One who works at a transportation professional company.",
      "One who works at organizations and institutions.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "One who drives a vehicle.",
    id: 89,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whose duty is it to confirm the condition of the vehicle before driving it?",
    options: [
      "Traffic Police's.",
      "Mechanical Engineer's.",
      "Driver's.",
      "Transportation Management Office's.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Driver's.",
    id: 90,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done to stop the vehicle immediately?",
    options: [
      "Use brakes safely.",
      "Blow horn.",
      "Ask the traffic police.",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Use brakes safely.",
    id: 91,
  },
  {
    question: "From where can water leak into the engine?",
    options: [
      "From the silencer pipe.",
      "From the gauge pipe that checks engine oil.",
      "From the air cleaner.",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above.",
    id: 92,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of a speedometer?",
    options: [
      "Measure the speed of the vehicle.",
      "Measure the temperature of the vehicle.",
      "Measure the fuel in the vehicle.",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above.",
    id: 93,
  },
  {
    question: "In what condition does the brake light glow?",
    options: [
      "While changing gears.",
      "While pressing the accelerator.",
      "While using foot brake.",
      "While blowing horn.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "While using foot brake.",
    id: 94,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of a spark plug?",
    options: [
      "To ignite the mixture of air & fuel in the engine.",
      "To provide the quantity of water to the engine.",
      "To provide mobil to the engine.",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To ignite the mixture of air & fuel in the engine.",
    id: 95,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the device that adds the quantity of air & fuel in the carburetor?",
    options: ["Spark plug", "Clutch", "Battery", "Throttle"],
    correctAnswer: "Throttle",
    id: 96,
  },
  {
    question: "What does a master cylinder do?",
    options: [
      "Helps the vehicle run.",
      "Helps the vehicle go up.",
      "Helps the vehicle go back.",
      "Helps the vehicle stop.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Helps the vehicle stop.",
    id: 97,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following engines has a carburetor?",
    options: [
      "Petrol engine.",
      "Diesel engine.",
      "Electric engine.",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Petrol engine.",
    id: 98,
  },
  {
    question: "What are the two devices that increase the speed of a vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Brakes and accelerators.",
      "Accelerators and steering.",
      "Gear and accelerator.",
      "Fan belt and accelerator.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Gear and accelerator.",
    id: 99,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be done if there is a red light in the oil pressure meter situated on the dashboard?",
    options: [
      "One should start the engine.",
      "One should stop the engine.",
      "One should use brake.",
      "One should blow horn.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "One should stop the engine.",
    id: 100,
  },
  {
    question: "What's kept in the radiator?",
    options: ["Petrol", "Diesel", "Water", "Acid"],
    correctAnswer: "Water",
    id: 101,
  },
  {
    question: "In which gear should you start the engine?",
    options: ["First gear", "Second gear", "Third gear", "Neutral"],
    correctAnswer: "Neutral",
    id: 102,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should one do when the vehicle emits black smoke while starting?",
    options: [
      "Close the silencer pipe.",
      "Remove the silencer pipe.",
      "Take the vehicle to the workshop to repair the engine.",
      "Ignore it.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Take the vehicle to the workshop to repair the engine.",
    id: 103,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the meter that measures the power of the battery?",
    options: ["Lactometer", "Speedometer", "Hydrometer", "Ampere meter"],
    correctAnswer: "Ampere meter",
    id: 104,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done while reversing the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "Stop the vehicle.",
      "Use the reverse gear.",
      "Slowly back the vehicle using a looking glass.",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above.",
    id: 105,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of a clutch?",
    options: [
      "Increase speed",
      "Decrease speed",
      "Free engine from gear",
      "Stop the vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Free engine from gear",
    id: 106,
  },
  {
    question: "What is consumed while using A/C in a vehicle?",
    options: ["Power", "Fuel", "Both A and B", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: "Both A and B",
    id: 107,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main function of the gear box?",
    options: [
      "Only to run the vehicle speedily",
      "Only to run the vehicle slowly",
      "To maintain the desired speed",
      "Help the vehicle come across the ditch",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To maintain the desired speed",
    id: 108,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of brakes?",
    options: [
      "Stop the vehicle.",
      "Speed up the vehicle.",
      "To reverse the vehicle.",
      "To turn the vehicle.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stop the vehicle.",
    id: 109,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the fuel meter indicate?",
    options: [
      "Level of fuel",
      "Level of water",
      "Level of mobil",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above.",
    id: 110,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done to save the vehicle’s tires?",
    options: [
      "Drive at top gear",
      "To drive using less air",
      "Maintain the air pressure",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Maintain the air pressure",
    id: 111,
  },
  {
    question: "What might happen if the vehicle’s engine heats up too much?",
    options: [
      "The engine might wind up (rotate) more",
      "The engine might get an electric shock",
      "The engine might cease",
      "Nothing happens",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The engine might cease",
    id: 112,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of the carburetor?",
    options: [
      "To cool the engine.",
      "To heat up the engine.",
      "To help increase or decrease the engine`s speed.",
      "To mix up air & fuel as needed.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To mix up air & fuel as needed.",
    id: 113,
  },
  {
    question: "What should the driver not check before driving?",
    options: ["Lights", "Air in Wheels", "Color of the vehicle", "Brake"],
    correctAnswer: "Color of the vehicle",
    id: 114,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be done if gear oil drips continuously from the differential?",
    options: [
      "To add oil in time and drive the vehicle",
      "To repair it immediately",
      "To keep on driving until a sound comes",
      "To keep on driving until the engine heats up.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To repair it immediately",
    id: 115,
  },
  {
    question: "What controls the vehicle’s wheel?",
    options: ["Engine", "Brakes", "Body", "Battery"],
    correctAnswer: "Brakes",
    id: 116,
  },
  {
    question: "When is the reverse light turned on?",
    options: [
      "While using brakes",
      "While using hand brakes",
      "While pressing the accelerator",
      "While reversing the vehicle.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "While reversing the vehicle.",
    id: 117,
  },
  {
    question: "What is compressed in the diesel engine`s cylinder?",
    options: ["Water", "Fuel", "Air", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "Air",
    id: 118,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be checked if the footbrake stops working properly all of a sudden?",
    options: [
      "To check wheel’s pressure",
      "To check brake oil level",
      "To check master cylinder",
      "All of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above.",
    id: 119,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done if the engine doesn’t start in winter?",
    options: [
      "Turn on A/C",
      "Add water in mobil",
      "Add fuel.",
      "Start after using choke.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Start after using choke.",
    id: 120,
  },
  {
    question: "How does the battery used in a vehicle get charged?",
    options: [
      "By vehicle mobil",
      "By vehicle’s radiator",
      "By vehicle’s dynamo",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "By vehicle’s dynamo",
    id: 121,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of the dipstick?",
    options: [
      "To check the level of mobil",
      "To check the level of water",
      "To maintain the level of oil.",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To check the level of mobil",
    id: 122,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of an accelerator?",
    options: [
      "To cool the engine",
      "To close the oil.",
      "To help provide oil on the basis of speed",
      "To measure smoke",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To help provide oil on the basis of speed",
    id: 123,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of differential?",
    options: [
      "Turn wheels with different speed.",
      "To pump up air in wheels",
      "To patch up puncture.",
      "None of the above.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Turn wheels with different speed.",
    id: 124,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main function of the vehicle’s axle?",
    options: [
      "To bear the load of the vehicle and help the wheel turn.",
      "To only bear the load of the vehicle.",
      "To use Engine",
      "To use four wheels",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "To bear the load of the vehicle and help the wheel turn.",
    id: 125,
  },
  {
    question: "What is a wiper?",
    options: [
      "Device to increase speed.",
      "Device to stop the vehicle.",
      "Towel to wipe the vehicle.",
      "Device to clean the glass.",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Device to clean the glass.",
    id: 126,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the machine that generates electricity in a running engine?",
    options: ["Storage Battery", "Charging Dynamo", "Dry cell", "Torchlight"],
    correctAnswer: "Charging Dynamo",
    id: 127,
  },
  {
    question: "What do we call a petrol engine in other words?",
    options: [
      "Diesel engine",
      "Hydraulic engine",
      "Gasoline engine",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Gasoline engine",
    id: 128,
  },
  {
    question: "In what condition using the handbrake is considered dangerous?",
    options: [
      "While moving upwards",
      "While moving downwards",
      "At the time of high speed.",
      "In turnings",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "While moving upwards",
    id: 129,
  },
  {
    question: "Where does the steering work?",
    options: [
      "All the front wheels",
      "At the back wheels",
      "At the gear",
      "At the engine",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All the front wheels",
    id: 130,
  },
  {
    question: "Where does the brakes work on the vehicle?",
    options: [
      "At the engine",
      "At the steering",
      "At the wheels",
      "At the gear",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "At the wheels",
    id: 131,
  },
  {
    question: "On which systems are brakes based?",
    options: ["Mechanical", "Hydraulic system", "Both a & b", "None of them."],
    correctAnswer: "Both a & b",
    id: 132,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What should be added if the level of water decreases in the battery?",
    options: ["Tap`s water", "Distilled water", "Mineral water", "Mustard oil"],
    correctAnswer: "Distilled water",
    id: 133,
  },
  {
    question: "When should the choke lever be closed?",
    options: [
      "After the engine stops.",
      "Any time.",
      "After the engine starts",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "After the engine starts",
    id: 134,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done if black smoke comes while driving?",
    options: [
      "To add fuel",
      "To repair the engine",
      "To close the silencer pipe.",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "All of the above",
    id: 135,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Among the options, which one is the device that measures the speed of the running vehicle?",
    options: ["Hydrometer", "Thermal meter", "Hectometer", "Speedometer"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 136,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main source of electricity in the engine?",
    options: ["Petrol", "Battery", "Mobil", "Diesel"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 137,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options below which one doesn't help the engine stop?",
    options: [
      "Running at lower speed",
      "If engine remains in right condition",
      "If fuel is consumed",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 138,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the minimum displacement volume of engine in four wheeler used in driving school?",
    options: ["796 c.c.", "798 c.c.", "797 c.c.", "795 c.c."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 139,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much electrical power has been specified for three-wheeler electric vehicles for driving school?",
    options: ["1000 watts", "800 watts", "900 watts", "700 watts"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 140,
  },
  {
    question: "What makes the wheels of the vehicle turn?",
    options: ["Radiator", "Gear", "Differential", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 141,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main source of electricity in the engine?",
    options: ["Petrol", "Battery", "Mobil", "Diesel"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 137,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options below which one doesn't help the engine stop?",
    options: [
      "Running at lower speed",
      "If engine remains in right condition",
      "If fuel is consumed",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 138,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the minimum displacement volume of the engine in a four-wheeler used in driving school?",
    options: ["796 c.c.", "798 c.c.", "797 c.c.", "795 c.c."],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 139,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How much electrical power has been specified for three-wheeler electric vehicles for driving school?",
    options: ["1000 watts", "800 watts", "900 watts", "700 watts"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 140,
  },
  {
    question: "What makes the wheels of the vehicle turn?",
    options: ["Radiator", "Gear", "Differential", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 141,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options, what isn't kept in the radiator?",
    options: ["Petrol", "Diesel", "Acid", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 142,
  },
  {
    question: "What increases/decreases the power of the engine?",
    options: ["Accelerator", "Brake", "Steering", "Clutch"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 143,
  },
  {
    question: "What provides current to the vehicle’s engine?",
    options: ["Accelerator", "Clutch", "Steering", "Spark plug"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 144,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the function of a dynamo?",
    options: [
      "To supply current to the engine",
      "To cool the water of the radiator",
      "To charge the battery",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 145,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options, what makes the vehicular parts oily?",
    options: ["Grease", "Mobil", "Steering oil", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 146,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options, what is used to measure the fuel?",
    options: ["Speedometer", "Thermometer", "Telescope", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 147,
  },
  {
    question: "When are brakes not used?",
    options: [
      "While increasing the speed",
      "While turning the vehicle",
      "While reserving the vehicle",
      "While stopping the vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 148,
  },
  {
    question: "What should be done before driving?",
    options: [
      "To inspect the condition of the vehicle",
      "To inform the traffic",
      "To inform to a mechanical engineer",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 149,
  },
  {
    question: "What drives the fan?",
    options: ["Accelerator", "Clutch", "Fan belt", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 150,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following indicates the level of fuel in the vehicle?",
    options: ["Fuel gauge", "Speedometer", "Thermometer", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 151,
  },
  {
    question: "What is not the main function of the accelerator?",
    options: [
      "To heat the engine",
      "To close/stop oil",
      "To decrease pollution",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 152,
  },
  {
    question: "Where does the steering not work?",
    options: ["At gear", "At engine", "At brake", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 153,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the brake not work at?",
    options: ["At engine", "At gear", "At steering", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 154,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the main source of electricity in vehicles?",
    options: ["Fuel", "Engine", "Dynamo", "Battery"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 155,
  },
  {
    question: "What supplies mobil to different parts?",
    options: ["Choke", "Oil pump", "Carburetor", "All of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 156,
  },
  {
    question: "Which oil is used in the engine?",
    options: ["Kerosene", "Brake oil", "Mobil", "Diesel"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 157,
  },
  {
    question: "What is needed to start the diesel engine?",
    options: ["Diesel and air", "Spark plug", "Petrol and air", "Current"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 158,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which part does not work well if the wheels of the vehicle are underwater?",
    options: ["Light", "Clutch", "Footbrake", "Handbrake"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 159,
  },
  {
    question: "What does it mean by C.C. in a vehicle?",
    options: [
      "The volume of engine cylinder",
      "Capacity of brake",
      "Capacity of gearbox",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 160,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options, which one is the function of a workshop?",
    options: [
      "To repair broken vehicles",
      "To do the finishing of vehicles",
      "To build the body of the vehicle",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 161,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the options, what is the function of a driving school?",
    options: [
      "To help fill up a license form",
      "To help register the license form",
      "To help in trial examination",
      "To instruct how to drive",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 162,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the color of the pollution sticker?",
    options: ["Green", "Blue", "Yellow", "Red"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 163,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What happens if one drives without testing the vehicle’s pollution level?",
    options: ["Imprisonment", "Fine", "Both a and b", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 164,
  },
  {
    question: "How often is the government vehicle’s pollution test done?",
    options: [
      "Every 6 months",
      "Every year",
      "Every Two years",
      "Every three months",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 165,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the green sticker used in a vehicle indicate?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle pollution is checked",
      "Vehicle without pollution",
      "Both a and b",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 166,
  },
  {
    question: "Among the vehicles below, which one doesn't emit smoke?",
    options: ["Bus", "Mini bus", "Truck", "Trolleybus"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 167,
  },
  {
    question: "How can pollution be decreased?",
    options: [
      "Using A/C & heater less",
      "By keeping the engine in good condition",
      "By driving the vehicle less",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 168,
  },
  {
    question: "Where is vehicular pollution law/regulation implemented?",
    options: [
      "In Kathmandu Valley",
      "In Birgunj market",
      "In Biratnagar Metropolitan",
      "All over Nepal",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 169,
  },
  {
    question: "What is meant by vehicle pollution?",
    options: [
      "Mobil used in engine",
      "Fuel kept in vehicle",
      "Dirt in the vehicle",
      "Smoke coming from the vehicle",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 302,
  },
  {
    question: "Which part of the vehicle affects vehicular pollution?",
    options: ["Brake", "Gearbox", "Fuel", "The condition of the engine"],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 303,
  },
  {
    question: "Which engine produces the least pollution?",
    options: [
      "Diesel engine",
      "Petrol engine",
      "Electric engine",
      "Coal engine",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 304,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of pollution is made by the horn?",
    options: [
      "Air pollution",
      "Soil pollution",
      "Water pollution",
      "Sound pollution",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 305,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which vehicular engine, among two-stroke and four-stroke engines, makes more pollution?",
    options: ["Two-stroke", "Four-stroke", "Both of them", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 306,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What kind of vehicle is more suitable for making a city pollution-free?",
    options: ["Electric", "Diesel", "Petrol", "Gas"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 307,
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the pollution level of EV (Electric Vehicle) checked?",
    options: [
      "Department of Transport Management",
      "Electricity Authority",
      "Transportation Management Office",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 308,
  },
  {
    question: "In which area should the horn not be blown?",
    options: [
      "Main road",
      "Area where there is a traffic jam",
      "Area near school and hospital",
      "Area where there is a demonstration",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 309,
  },
  {
    question: "From which part of the vehicle does smoke exit?",
    options: ["Silencer", "Engine", "Gear", "Axle"],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 310,
  },
  {
    question: "Which is the prevailing pollution standard in Nepal?",
    options: ["2054 B.S.", "2049 B.S.", "2069 B.S.", "2056 B.S."],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 311,
  },
  {
    question: "Why is the vehicular pollution test done?",
    options: [
      "To know the condition of the vehicle",
      "To save the vehicle from an accident",
      "Both a and b",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 312,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Among the vehicles mentioned below, to which kind of vehicle is vehicular pollution Standards, 2069 not applicable?",
    options: [
      "Private vehicles",
      "Large buses",
      "Heavy equipment like dozer loaders etc.",
      "All of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 314,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What happens if one drives the vehicle with no pollution-free sticker in the restricted area?",
    options: [
      "Fine",
      "Confiscation of the vehicle",
      "Imprisonment",
      "Both a and b",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 315,
  },
  {
    question: "What kind of vehicle’s pollution is not checked?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle run by petrol",
      "Electric vehicle",
      "Vehicle run by Diesel",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 316,
  },
  {
    question: "Which office doesn't do vehicular pollution test?",
    options: [
      "Vehicle Fitness Test Center",
      "Transportation Management Office",
      "Traffic Police Office",
      "None of them",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 317,
  },
  {
    question: "What is normally checked in a vehicular pollution test?",
    options: ["Brake", "Body", "Smoke", "Fuel"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 318,
  },
  {
    question: "Which office does the work of vehicle fitness test?",
    options: [
      "Ministry for Physical Infrastructure and Transport",
      "Department of Transport Management",
      "Traffic Police Office",
      "Transport Management Office",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 319,
  },
  {
    question: "What color sticker is attached to safa(clean) tempo?",
    options: ["Blue", "Red", "Green", "None of them"],
    correctAnswer: 2,
    id: 320,
  },
  {
    question: "Which pollution is caused by vehicular smoke?",
    options: [
      "Air pollution",
      "Soil pollution",
      "Water pollution",
      "Sound pollution",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 0,
    id: 321,
  },
  {
    question: "Which fuel causes more pollution?",
    options: ["Electrical", "Diesel", "Petrol", "Gas"],
    correctAnswer: 1,
    id: 322,
  },
  {
    question: "For what kind of vehicle is a fitness certificate needed?",
    options: [
      "Private vehicle",
      "Rental vehicle",
      "Government vehicle",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: 3,
    id: 323,
  },
];

export const englishCardDetails = [
  {
    topic: "Random",
    questions: 500,
    link: "english/bike/random",
    imageLink:'/assets/steer-wheel.svg'
  },
  {
    topic: "Driving Knowledge",
    questions: 130,
    link: "/english/bike/knowledge",
    imageLink : '/assets/steer-wheel.svg'
  },
  {
    topic: "Regulations Knowledge",
    questions: 90,
    link: "english/bike/regulations"
    ,imageLink: '/assets/scale-icon.svg'
  },
  {
    topic: "Mechanical Knowledge",
    questions: 80,
    link: "english/bike/mechanical",
    imageLink : '/assets/engine-gears-icon.svg'
  },
  {
    topic: "Environmental Knowledge",
    questions: 30,
    link: "english/bike/environment",
    imageLink:'/assets/earth.svg'
  },
  {
    topic: "Accidents Knowledge",
    questions: 60,
    link: "english/bike/accidents",
    imageLink:'/assets/bike-accident-icon.svg'
  },
  {
    topic: "Traffic Signals",
    questions: 110,
    link: "english/bike/signals",
    imageLink:'/assets/trafic.svg'
  },
  
];

